<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.ti.ccstudio.cc26xx.devicesupport.linux"
      label="CC26xx Device Support"
      version="3.20.01.32"
      provider-name="Texas Instruments"
      os="linux">

   <copyright>
      Copyright Texas Instruments 2021
   </copyright>

   <license>
      See Code Composer Studio license for specific terms and conditions.
   </license>

   <description>
CC13xx/CC26xx Device Support
Version: 3.20.00
Date: 2024-05-03

This readme lists all relevant changes to the CC13xx/CC26xx Device support package.
- Changes marked [CC26x0] apply to all CC13x0 and CC26x0 devices.
- Changes marked [CC26x2] apply to all CC13x2 and CC26x2 devices.
- Changes marked [CC26x4] apply to all CC13x4 and CC26x4 devices.
- Other changes apply to all supported devices.

-------------------------
Release Notes:
-------------------------
Version 3.20.1.32 (2024-07-09):
- [CC27xx] Added permission check of both CCFG and SCFG. This is to protect from locking the device by accident (LPRFTOOLS-1562)


-------------------------
Troubleshooting:
-------------------------
- Mass erase device with CPU inaccessible:
  The default target configuration files for CC13xx/CC26xx devices enable
  "custom configuration" for all subpaths to enable debugging in low power
  modes. If the CPU DAP is inaccessible (e.g. locked in CCFG), CCS will not be
  able to connect to Icepick to issue Mass Erase. To get around this, open the
  target configuration file (.ccxml) and disable "custom configuration" on
  *all* subpaths.
  Steps to issue mass erase:
  1. Launch target configuration file.
  2. In Debug view, select Scripts &gt; CC26xx &gt; MassErase().

-------------------------
Release History:
Version 3.20.10.25 (2024-06-07):
- [CC27xx] Added support to get HSM System Information and HSM FW Update status (PG 2.0 or newer only)(LPRFTOOLS-1531)
- [CC27xx] Added erase options to enable use of the SACI command to do "erase main only" (PG 2.0 or newer only) (LPRFTOOLS-1522)
Version 3.20.00.16 (2024-05-03):
- [CC27xx] Added support for PG 2.0  (LPRFTOOLS-1545)
- [CC27xx] Added support for programming of HSM FW image (PG 2.0 or newer only) (LPRFTOOLS-1545)
- [CC27xx] Added support to clear address bit 28. This indicate non-secure address space (PG 1.x only) (LPRFTOOLS-1534)
Version 3.19.00.12 (2024-03-08):
- [CC23xx/CC27xx] Added support to program CCFG user record with binary file as input (LPRFTOOLS-1439)
- [CC23xx/CC27xx] Improved method to enter SACI mode when the reset pin is not connected (LPRFTOOLS-1525)
Version 3.19.00.9 (2024-02-16):
- [CC23xx] Added device support for CC2340R22 and CC2340R53 (LPRFTOOLS-1493, LPRFTOOLS-1494)
- [CC27xx] New property added in device file to support "Fake Standby" (LPRFTOOLS-1498)
- [CC23xx/CC27xx] Support J-Link. New GEL script to modify the reset methods (LPRFTOOLS-1451)
- [CC13x4/CC26x4] Updated revision translation to support PG 3.0 (LPRFTOOLS-1490)
Version 3.18.00.8 (2024-01-05):
- [CC23xx/CC27xx] - Added device support support: CC2340R2, CC2744R7, CC2745R7, CC2745R10, CC2745P10, CC2755R10, CC2755P10 (LPRFTOOLS-1466)
Version 3.17.10.26 (2023-06-27):
- [CC23xx] - Flashloader updated to support stand alone image verification in UniFlash (GUI/CLI) (LPRFTOOLS-1420)
           - Flashloader updated to support seamless programming of "locked" device (LPRFTOOLS-1420)
Version 3.17.10.24 (2023-03-28):
- [CC23xx] Updated register descriptions (DOC release 2.8.17)
- [CC13x4/CC26x4] Updated register descriptions (DOC release 20230119_SRC47).
Version 3.17.09.20 (2023-03-28):
- [CC23xx] Updated register descriptions (DOC release 2.8.7)
- [CC13x4/CC26x4] Updated register descriptions (DOC release 20230119_SRC47).
Version 3.17.08.15 (2022-12-07):
- [CC23xx] Added device support: CC2340R5.
- [CC13x4/CC26x4] Updated register descriptions (DOC release) (LPRFTOOLS-1362).
- [CC13x4/CC26x4] Power profiling definitions updated (LPRFTOOLS-1371).
-------------------------
Version 3.16.11.152 (2022-09-02):
- [CC13x4/CC26x4] The Symbol file for debugging of the ROM code has been updated for revision B (LPRFTOOLS-1344, LPRFTOOLS-1334)
- [CC13x4/CC26x4] Updated flash properties to recognize device revision B  (LPRFTOOLS-1343)
- [CC13x4/CC26x4] The module and register documentation updated (LPRFTOOLS-1343)
- [CC13x2/CC26x2] Fixed issue with "Unknown" revision shown in the log window when debugging revision F device (LPRFTOOLS-1342)
Version 3.16.10.134 (2022-05-24):
- Added device support: CC1312PSIP. (LPRFTOOLS-1301)
- [CC13x2/CC26x2, CC1311/CC2651, CC23xx] Updated register descriptions. (LPRFTOOLS-1320)
- [CC13x4/CC26x4] The Symbol file for debugging of the ROM code has been updated to solve issue when trying to start CCS ROV (RTOS Object Viewer) (LPRFTOOLS-1247)
Version 3.16.09.113 (2022-02-21):
- Added device support: CC2651R3SIPA, CC2652PSIP, CC2652RSIP and CC2662R1F. (LPRFTOOLS-1230, LPRFTOOLS-1229, LPRFTOOLS-1228 and LPRFTOOLS-1227)
- [CC26x4] Fixed flash programming error for "All Unprotected Sectors" erase option. (LPRFTOOLS-957, LPRFTOOLS-1223)
- [CC26x2] Updated register descriptions. (LPRFTOOLS-1176, LPRFTOOLS-1175, LPRFTOOLS-1158)
- Added default hex build options for GNU and TI Clang toolchain for all devices. (LPRFTOOLS-1154)
- Fixed flash loader issue for CC2653P10. (LPRFTOOLS-1153)
- [CC26x4] Updated register descriptions. (LPRFTOOLS-1136)
- Fixed minor issues in flash loader (LPRFTOOLS-1101)
Version 3.16.08.48 (2021-09-21):
- Created separate target flash loaders for CC13x1 and CC26x1 devices and for CC13x2x7 and CC26x2x7 devices (LPRFTOOLS-1126)
Version 3.16.07.46 (2021-08-27):
- Added device support: CC2674R10, CC2674P10, CC1354R10, CC1354P10, CC1314R10 and CC2653P10
- Previous speed improvements for flash programming has been reverted to ensure better robustness (LPRFTOOLS-970)
- The error message given when flash programming fails has been improved to give a better description (LPRFTOOLS-992)
Version 3.15.03.123 (2021-03-10):
- Fixed issue with flashloader for CC13x1 and CC26x1 devices (LPRFTOOLS-964)
Version 3.15.02.121 (2021-02-03):
- Added device support: CC2672R, CC2672P (LPRFTOOLS-882)
Version 3.15.00.117 (2020-12-08):
- Fixed issue with reference to peripheral module that has been removed for the CC1311x/CC2651x devices (LPRFTOOLS-895)
- Updated register description of peripheral modules for CC26x2x7/CC13x2x7 devices (LPRFTOOLS-879)
Version 3.15.00.111 (2020-11-05):
- Added device support: CC1311R3, CC1311P3, CC2651R3, CC2651P3
Version 3.14.02.110 (2020-11-04):
- Fixed issue with file name of the flashloader to be used for CC26x2R7/CC13x2R7 devices
Version 3.14.01.105 (2020-10-19):
- New devices renamed: CC2652R7, CC2652P7, CC1312R7, CC1352P7 (LPRFTOOLS-875).
Version 3.14.00.93 (2020-04-08):
- Added device support: CC2652R1F6, CC2652P1F6, CC1312R1F6, CC1352P1F6 (LPRFTOOLS-850,851,856,857).
Version 3.13.00.92 (2020-04-07):
- Added device support: CC2640R2L (LPRFTOOLS-849).
Version 3.12.01.84 (2020-01-30):
- Improve flash programming performance by reducing wait time (LPRFTOOLS-829).
Version 3.12.00.79 (2019-07-01):
- Added driverlib ROM symbols to list of symbols automatically loaded when programming a device (LPRFTOOLS-703).
  Driverlib and TI-RTOS ROM symbols can also be loaded at any time from CCS Scripts menu.
- Added device support: CC2652P1F (LPRFTOOLS-774).
Version 3.11.01.77 (2019-03-21):
- Added address information for CCFG and FCFG1 areas to the device flash property XML files.
  This enables Uniflash GUI users to easily select, and read, these memory ranges from a
  dropdown in the Memory View (LPRFTOOLS-778, UNIFLASH-890).
- Fixed issue where version string was not correctly displayed by Linux and OSX flashloader
  binaries (LPRFTOOLS-701). You can see the flashloader version by running for example:
  - Linux: strings libFlashCC26x2.so | grep VERSION
  - OSX  : strings libFlashCC26x2.dylib | grep VERSION
- Added target connection files (.ccxml) for all CC13xx/CC26xx devices for use with the
  Uniflash command line tool. The files are located in the ccs_base/arm/ folder (LPRFTOOLS-788).

Version 3.11.00.68 (2018-10-29):
- Added device support: CC2652RB1F (LPRFTOOLS-684).
- Added support for CRC verification during program load (LPRFTOOLS-690).
  This option speeds up verification during program load and verifies that all data was
  programmed to flash successfully. This option is enabled by default.
  Steps to enable/disable CRC verification in CCS/Uniflash:
  - GUI: Check/uncheck "Use CRC Verification during Program Load" checkbox
  - CLI: Use "--setting CrcVerify=X" X=0 to disable, X=1 to enable (default)
- Added blank check support in flashloader library (LPRFTOOLS-694).
  - GUI: Click "Perform Blank Check" button, result will be displayed in the console.
  - CLI: Use opcode "BlankCheck", e.g. "dslite -c device.ccxml --before BlankCheck"
- CLI now supports mass erase using "-O MassErase" (LPRFTOOLS-660).
  This implementation only works for devices with locked debug interface if the CCXML file used
  has "custom configuration" disabled for all subpaths. See Troubleshooting section for details.
- Flashloader now displays device revision letter in addition to major.minor version (UNIFLASH-1134, LPRFTOOLS-523).
  Example: "Rev E (2.1)" for CC2652R1F.
- [CC26x2] Flashloader now reports revision E (2.1) for devices with DEVICE_ID.PG_REV = 0x3 (LPRFTOOLS-657).
- [CC26x2] Register definition files and linker files updated for revision E (2.1) (LPRFTOOLS-662).
- [CC26x2] Added TI-RTOS ROM symbols for device revision E (2.1) (LPRFTOOLS-656).
- File size of all TI-RTOS ROM symbol files has been reduced by stripping away unnecessary information (LPRFTOOLS-678).
- [CC26x2] Device XML files now enable XDS emulators to perform workaround for device hardware issue (LPRFTOOLS-617).
  This change allows XDS emulators to connect to device while it is in low-power mode without using halt-in-boot.
- Added version information to flashloader library (LPRFTOOLS-514).
- This is the first release supporting win64 platforms (LPRFTOOLS-329).

Version 3.10.10.02 (2018-06-07):
- [CC26x2] Renamed field MCU_PD in digital states to MCU_CTL as CC13x2/CC26x2 devices do not have
  an MCU power domain. The bit represents the active/non-active of the MCU controller state.
- Added feature to enable 'debug lock', 'write-protect flash sectors' or 'disable Bootloader' options
  in CCFG memory (UNIFLASH-1006, UNIFLASH-1007, UNIFLASH-1036).
- Added feature to skip programming of pages filled with given value (UNIFLASH-312).
- Added feature to erase specific flash sectors as standalone operation or during program load (UNIFLASH-310, UNIFLASH-311).
- CC2640R2F silicon revision is now correctly reported as 2.5. Was previously reported as revision 1.0 (LPRFTOOLS-628).

Version 3.10.02.00 (2018-04-23):
- [CC26x2] Minor change to the device XML files that allows XDS emulators to connect
  to a device while it is in low power mode (LPRFTOOLS-617, DBGTRC-3614).

Version 3.10.01.00 (2018-04-03):
- Corrected syntactic issues with some device register files (LPRFTOOLS-614).

Version 3.10.00.02 (2018-03-12):
- Removed spaces from EnergyTrace++ names, e.g. "PC Error" changed to "PC_Error".
- Added feature to retain secondary BLE and IEEE address during program load (UNIFLASH-693, UNIFLASH-694).
- Added feature to override secondary BLE and IEEE address during program load (UNIFLASH-692, UNIFLASH-691).
- Added feature to skip specific pages during program load (UNIFLASH-313, UNIFLASH-315).
- [CC26x2] Peripheral description files updated, dated February 1 2018 (LPRFTOOLS-604).
- [CC26x0] Peripheral description files updated, dated January 24 2018 (LPRFTOOLS-604).
- Fixed some potential issues in the host flashloader library found during static code analysis (LPRFTOOLS-602).

Version 3.02.04.00 (2018-01-29):
- [CC26x2] EnergyTrace++: Updated / corrected digital state info bitfields (LPRFTOOLS-370).
- [CC26x0] EnergyTrace++: Added digital state info field indicating program counter value error.

Version 3.02.03.00 (2018-01-09):
- Added GEL functions for use Uniflash 4.2.2 command line tool (dslite).
  Added function for listing available commands and performing pin reset (LPRFTOOLS-531).

Version 3.02.02.00 (2017-12-01):
- Fixed issue where some CCS 7.4.0 users observed data verification errors.
  The target flashloader now stores FLASH cache configuration and disables
  caching before executing a command. The initial cache configuration is restored
  when command is complete (LPRFTOOLS-525).
- Fixed minor issue with host library printing scrambled error code if
  target flashloader timed out while executing command (LPRFTOOLS-526).

Version 3.02.01.00 (2017-11-15):
- Radio core RAM sections added to memory map. Debuggers are now allowed to
  read/write these memory sections (LPRFTOOLS-505).
- Fixed bug in flashloader library causing flash loading to fail when using
  erase setting "All unprotected sectors" (LPRFTOOLS-515).
- Target binaries rebuilt using CCS 7.3.0.00019.

Version 3.02.00.00 (2017-11-02):
- Reset "Board Reset (free run)" now enabled from CCS reset menu. This reset
  pulls the target's RESET_N pin, making the target free run (LPRFTOOLS-461).
- Reset "Board Reset (automatic)" renamed to "Board Reset (automatic connect/disconnect)"
  to make it clearer what it does.
  NOTE: This name change may break backward compatibility with scripts using this reset (LPRFTOOLS-461).
- Peripheral description files updated, dated November 1, 2017 (LPRFTOOLS-442).
- [CC26x2] Fixed issue with GEL file inhibiting debugger from reading all of
  CCFG area which is memory mapped to 0x50003000 (LPRFTOOLS-455).

Version 3.01.01.01 (2017-10-06):
- Linux binaries rebuilt fixing dependency issue observed on Ubuntu 14.04 (LPRFTOOLS-450).

Version 3.01.01.00 (2017-09-18):
- Fixed problem where flashloader didn't output the read value for the following
  operations in dslite (CLI): ReadPriBle, ReadPriIeee, ReadSecBle, ReadSecIeee (LPRFTOOLS-414).

Version 3.01.00.00 (2017-08-15):
- Device name CC1354R1F3 changed to CC1352P1F3 (LPRFTOOLS-405).
  This will break CCS projects created with device CC1354R1F3. The
  workaround is to update CCS project to device CC1352P1F3.

Version 3.00.02.00 (2017-06-16):
- Minor updates to flash property XML for all properties to show in
  CCS Uniflash (LPRFTOOLS-362).

Version 3.00.01.00 (2017-05-19):
- Fixed issue where CCS did not run to main if the CPU interrupt vector table was
  at a non-zero address (LPRFTOOLS-340).
- Fixed issue where program load in some cases led to an "Unable to access the DAP" error.
  This was only possible to work around by using Mass Erase from the CCS Script menu (LPRFTOOLS-325).

Version 3.00.00.00 (2017-05-12):
- Added support for CC26x2 device family, this has led to some restructuring of
  the package, and renaming of files (LPRFTOOLS-327).
- [CC26x2] New devices: CC1312R1F3, CC1352R1F3, CC1354R1F3, CC2642R1F, CC2652R1F.
- Improved the error message given if the writing to target data buffers fails (LPRFTOOLS-328).

Version 2.20.02.00 (2017-06-07):
- This is a hotfix release:
- Fixed bug in flashloader, causing verification issues in some cases.

Version 2.20.01.00 (2017-04-28):
- TI-RTOS ROM symbols are now automatically loaded when programming device (LPRFTOOLS-274).
  ROM symbols can also be loaded at any time from CCS Scripts menu.
- Improved flashloader feedback if erase or program fails.
- Flashloader verbosity can now be controlled using "Enable Verbose Mode" (LPRFTOOLS-315).
  In CCS: Tools &gt; On-Chip Flash and enable "Enable Verbose Mode" at the bottom.
  In Uniflash: Click "Verbose" button in the console output.

Version 2.20.00.02 (2017-03-28):
- Flashloader (host and target side) reworked to significantly increase performance (LPRFTOOLS-204).
  The best speed is achieved when using 4-pin cJTAG with erase option "All unprotected sectors".
- Added missing section to TI linker files (.cmd) to remove a warning seen by users using
  #pragma NOINIT(variableName) (LPRFTOOLS-303).
- Peripheral files updated (dated 2017-03-17).

Version 2.10.03.00 (2017-02-14):
- CC13x0/CC26x0 GEL files now block access to AON_RTC module while
  target is running. Fixes an issue where access to devices is lost
  when using ROV2 (LPRFTOOLS-292).

Version 2.10.02.01 (2017-01-31):
- Added support for XDS110 EnergyTrace++ for CC2650, CC1350, and
  CC2640R2F devices (LPRFTOOLS-279).

Version 2.10.01.00 (2016-12-16):
- Added missing device XML file for CC1310F32.

Version 2.10.00.00 (2016-12-02):
- Added erase setting "Necessary Sectors Only (Retain untouched content within sector)".
  This option is now default (LPRFTOOLS-82).
- Fixed issue where flashloader misinterpreted device SRAM size.
- Peripheral files updated (dated 2016-11-23).

Version 2.00.02.01 (2016-11-02):
- Flashloader library for Microsoft Windows rebuilt using VS2015 toolchain (LPRFTOOLS-245).

Version 2.00.02.00 (2016-09-29): (for CCS with J-Link support)
- Added device support: CC2640R2F (LPRFTOOLS-154).
- Fixed issue where sector erase sometimes failed on unaligned data sections.

Version 2.00.01.01 (2016-09-25): (for CCS with J-Link support)
- Rebuild of 2.00.01.00 on new version control system.

Version 2.00.01.00 (2016-09-09): (for CCS with J-Link support)
- Fixed issue where flashloader sometimes corrupted data (CCDSK-2235).

Version 2.00.00.00 (2016-06-30): (for CCS with J-Link support)
- Flashloader now uses iFlashDevice2 API to support Uniflash v4 (LPRFTOOLS-114).
- Added support for Uniflash 4 device information (UNIFLASH-308).
  This change requires CCS 6.2.0 or Uniflash 4.
- Added support for reading primary/secondary MAC addresses, and for
  writing secondary MAC addresses (UNIFLASH-317).
- Removed XDS560 properties from device XML files. XDS560 emulator is not
  supported (LPRFTOOLS-126).
- Fixed issue in linker files, now uses correct define
  __TI_COMPILER_VERSION__  (LPRFTOOLS-131).

Version 1.20.00.03 (2016-04-06): (for CCS with J-Link support)
- CC13xx/CC26xx device support package has been split into OS specific packages
  for win32, linux and OSX (LPRFTOOLS-100).
- Some filenames changed (e.g. cc26xx.gel renamed to cc26x0.gel)
- Linux: Flash loader rebuilt for 64bit.

Version 1.20.00.02 (2016-02-18): (for CCS with J-Link support)
- Changed default device connection from XDS100v3 to XDS110 (LPRFTOOLS-77).
- Removed preprocessor define "DEBUG", which was added to project settings
  when creating new project, but also when changing target connection file
  (LPRFTOOLS-55).
- Removed workaround for CCS issue requiring GEL files to disable memory map
  during download (SDSCM00052717), seen when using Segger J-Link. Issue has
  been fixed in CCS.
- Removed unsupported resets from CCS reset menu (J-Link GEL scripts).
- Fixed problem where HEX utility did not work out of the box (LPRFTOOLS-56).
- Updated register definition files for all CC13xx and CC26xx variants.

Version 1.20.00.01 (2015-12-07): (for CCS with J-Link support)
- Respin of 1.20.00 (CCS 6.1.3) including changes introduced in 1.16.00.00
  (CCS 6.1). Requires TI emulation drivers v6.0.83.0 or higher.
- See 1.20.00.00 release notes.

Version 1.16.00.00 (2015-12-07):
- This release is for CCS 6.1.x and requires XDS emupack 6.0.83.0 or higher.
- Default target configuration for XDS110 emulators changed to 2-pin cJTAG
  (LPRFTOOLS-46).
- Fixed problem where XDS200 target configuration didn't choose OSCAN5 by
  default.
- Corrected issue with GNU linker command files.

Version 1.20.00.00 (2015-12-04):
- This release requires CCS DebugServer 6.2.0.1426 or higher.
- GEL files updated to support J-Link debuggers from Segger.

Version 1.15.04.00 (2015-10-30):
- Flashloader now combines nearby sections into a single write to improve speed.
  This option can be disabled in CC26_FlashProperties.xml, or
  CC13_FlashProperties.xml, (located in ccs_base/DebugServer/propertyDB/) by
  removing all references to FlashAlignmentSize and FlashAlignCombineToggle.

Version 1.15.03.00 (2015-10-21):
- Updated register definition files for all CC13xx and CC26xx variants.
- Added GNU tool options for all CC13xx and CC26xx variants.

Version 1.15.02.00 (2015-09-04):
- Updated linker files with support for "ramfunc" attribute introduced in
  TI compiler version 15.9.0.STS.
  See http://processors.wiki.ti.com/index.php/Placing_functions_in_RAM

Version 1.15.01.01 (2015-08-28):
- Corrected issue with register width attribute in CPU_* peripherals

Version 1.15.01.00 (2015-08-20):
- Added GPRAM section to default linker files (LPRFTOOLS-2)
- Cleaned up GEL files (LPRFTOOLS-10)
- Fixed issue with flash loader library for 64bit OS (CCS on Mac) (LPRFTOOLS-5)

Version 1.15.00.00 (2015-06-04):
- Updated register definition files for all CC13xx and CC26xx variants.
- Added flash loader library for CCS on Mac (beta)

Version 1.14.00.01 (2015-05-27):
- Removed redundant file FlashDLLDB.xml.
  Added dependency to com.ti.dsflash.* v6.1.0.1247 and higher

Version 1.14.00.00 (2015-04-30):
- New devices: CC13xx rev 2.0 variants (5764)
  CC1350F128, CC1310F128, CC1310F64, CC1310F32
- Support for CC1310F128_REV1 is removed (no longer updated)
- Removed device preprocessor defines added during "New project" wizard
- Updated register definitions for all CC13xx and CC26xx variants.

Version 1.13.00.01 (2015-01-15):
- Removed redundant file FlashPropertiesTranslator.xml

Version 1.13.00.00 (2015-01-06):
- Version included in CCS 6.1
- Updated register definitions for all CC13xx and CC26xx variants.

Version 1.12.02.00 (2014-12-18):
- Fixes flash loader issue on devices where with system reset is configured
  to behaves as pin reset, also a board reset is issued before loading a program
  into device flash (5618).
- Updated device preprocessor defines added during "New project" wizard, e.g.
  define CC2650F128RGZ (5483).

Version 1.12.01.01 (2014-11-26):
- Fixes dependency problem in CCS Update Manager

Version 1.12.01.00 (2014-11-26):
- Flash properties: Default erase option changed to "Necessary Sectors Only" (5473)
- GEL script: Fixed issue seen when CM3 DAP is inaccessible (see Troubleshooting) (5481)

Version 1.12.00.00 (2014-11-07):
- New devices: CC2620F128
- Board reset is issued when initializing debug session (5437)
- Added device register description files
- Added flash properties: Erase type during program load
- Added flash properties: Keep Customer Configuration Area during program load

Version 1.11.00.00 (2014-09-10):
- New devices: CC2640F128, CC2630F128, CC1310F128_REV1
- Several bug fixes in CC26xx flash loader (5314, 5333, 5345)
- Updates to debugger memory map, added GPRAM, FCFG2, CCFG.
- Updates to CC26xx debugger memory map, removed read/write perimssions on clock gated
  EFUSE registers in FLASH module, range 0x4003.1000 - 0x4003.1FFF (5346)
- CC26xx board reset (CC26xx halt-in-boot) and mass erase available through GEL scripts.
- CC26xx flash erase button available through flash properties (5365)

Version 1.0.0.0 (2014-02-24):
- Initial version with CC2650F128 support
- Moved system reset from onFileLoaded() callback in cc26*.gel to flash loader library.
- Updated linker command files to support extended CCFG area, and to better support cross linking.
- Added default connection property to the device XML.
- Added family filtering property to the device XML (for CCS GUI).
- Tested with CCS v6 beta 3 (6.0.0.116)

</description>
</feature>
